In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to go over how to pronounce the Y consonant.
我们将学习如何发音 Y 辅音。
To make the Y sound,
要发出 Y 的声音，
the jaw drops a little bit.
下巴稍微下垂。
Yy.
Yy。
The lips may be relaxed,
嘴唇可以放松，
or they may begin to take the position of the next sound.
或者开始为下一个声音做准备。
The tongue tip is down,
舌尖向下，
lightly touching the back of the bottom front teeth.
轻轻触碰下前牙的后面。
The middle part of the tongue lifts and touches the roof of the mouth.
舌头的中部抬起并触碰上颚。
It pushes forward against the roof of the mouth before pulling away.
在拉开之前，它向前推压上颚。
As we push the tongue forward on the roof of the mouth,
当我们将舌头向前推压上颚时，
we close the vocal cords to get this sound, which we add to the sound, yy.
我们闭合声带以发出这个声音，然后加上声音，yy。
We release them the same time we release the tongue.
我们在释放舌头的同时释放声带。
Relaxed jaw drop, and the lips are relaxed.
放松下巴，下垂，嘴唇放松。
The tongue tip is down while the middle of the tongue presses forward against the roof of the mouth.
舌尖向下，而舌头的中部向前推压上颚。
The word yes.
单词 yes。
The tongue tip is down while the middle of the tongue presses forward against the roof of the mouth.
舌尖向下，而舌头的中部向前推压上颚。
The tongue releases into the EH as in BED vowel.
舌头释放进入 EH 如同 BED 的元音。
The word youth.
单词 youth。
Notice how the lips begin to round for the next sound.
注意嘴唇如何开始为下一个声音圆起。
The OO as in BOO vowel.
OO 如同 BOO 的元音。
Yell.
Yell。
The tongue tip is down while the middle of the tongue presses forward against the roof of the mouth,
舌尖向下，而舌头的中部向前推压上颚，
releasing into the EH as in BED vowel.
释放进入 EH 如同 BED 的元音。
This sound is most common at the beginning of words.
这个声音最常见于单词的开头。
It doesn't occur at the end of any words, though the letter Y does.
它不会出现在任何单词的结尾，尽管字母 Y 会。
The Y sound.
Y 的声音。
Yes.
Yes。
Youth.
Youth。
Yell.
Yell。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Yeah.
Yeah。
Unusual.
Unusual。
Senior.
Senior。
Y.
Y。
Senior.
Senior。
You.
You。
Y.
Y。
You.
You。
Yesterday.
Yesterday。
Y.
Y。
Yesterday.
Yesterday。
Yellow.
Yellow。
Y.
Y。
Yellow.
Yellow。